Yuki, look at how strong you've become.
Now let's take this monster down!
Miss Mira, I'm going to save you!
Thank you.
To be
continued...
A trump card?
This is going to be fun!
Now it's our turn! Great!
Slay support first!
Unpredictable.
Using chains big deal.
Look up.
So that's what happens when
you get caught in them?
They're not ordinary chains then.
Coco, now on, I'll save you both.
You're already defeated!
Stay out of this!
Yuki! Cover me!
I got you!
My angry cross!
Ah, how cute!
You stopped my attack!
No matter, a god's wrath
will always be felt!
Seriously?
It's one attack after the other!
This is getting old!
I'll keep drawing them in.
In the name of the Ozymas,
we will hold the line!
I'll be sure to live up to the
feelings he has put forth today.
Peaks of clouds above.
How many sink to lay bare?
Moonlit mountain.
Unshackle my mind of its limits!
My movements will be enhanced
for a short amount of time.
I developed this attack.
To defeat the eight thunder gods.
I'll show you the true might of a god?
Behold!
My breathtaking majesty!
She's only cloning her arms Ha ha ha!
Tremble in terror!
Before my million-fold divine punishment!
Picture it.
See it in your mind.
They broke through my multi-attack!
I was going for the kill!
A meaningless hit.
I'll push harder with the next one.
All right.
To be on the safe side, I'll send my
clones to deliver the final blow. Attack!
What's wrong with you?
Get out there and fight!
Mira!
Your clones are slow.
Looks like you haven't
absorbed Mira completely.
Knock it out!
Let's end this! Right!
Damn you, Mira!
You'll be fully consumed before long!
I am formidable!
I am a god!
I pledge myself fully.
To Miss Kyoka.
Yuki's banished.
No, wait!
Yuki's.
Inside her sword.
Accept your fate from
an all-powerful time!
Sword of servitude!
This launches me from inside her sword.
Using one of my lethal strikes!
I'll combine my heavenward power.
With my martial arts?
Ultimate dual technique.
They're still alive!
If you attempt to resist capture
or try to escape, you die.
Is this her default form?
Nika!
If you insist on trying to kill me...
Then it's time to bow down.
Heavenward.
You made the most of it.
Thank you.
Oh, I forgot what about
my sister and her friends?
Let me handle this Yuki.
Don't move or I'll shoot!
Looks like she got away.
Thank you for everything.
It looks like you conquered a god!
Relay the news of our enemy's defeat.
I'll secure the perimeter so
everything is safe. Copy that.
I'll write the report.
Leave the healing to me!
I've got plenty of energy left over!
That's right.
With Miss Tovera here, we'll
be back on our feet in no time.
I can finally breathe, but why
do I feel like I'm gonna...
Uhhh... Hey, you.
Kuusetsu!
Don't you worry.
None of this is actually real.
It's your dream state.
A mind palace of sorts.
Huh?
A dream?
This is all inside my mind?
I lost my physical form, so I had to
manifest what traces of my energy remained.
Energy?
You drank my divine
nectar, don't you remember?
Oh, right.
The thing about gods is, they
don't vanish into thin air.
My physical form is gone now,
and this is all that remains.
It's impossible for me to affect
the outside world, much less fight.
So you and I are left with no
other choice but to get along.
You're going to wake up now.
We can chat whenever you want.
You should feel lucky having such a
beautiful god living inside you. What?
Why should I feel so lucky?
Where am I?
In the 7th Squadron dorm! You're safe!
Uh... Uh...
Oh god!
Do you mean that whole
thing was just a dream?
I swear that was real, how?
You calm down right now!
That's an order!
Oh, okay.
You lost consciousness after
the battle in Yokohama.
You've been asleep for about two days.
I guess they brought me back
to headquarters to rest?
Your wounds have healed nicely.
So congrats!
You're in perfect health!
Everyone's at HQ,
and the commander is discussing
everything that happened back in Yokohama.
In that case, I should also be
helping and get back to work.
I don't think so.
Today you're going to rest.
Nei will handle all the cooking,
and you might want to take a bath.
Thank you.
I'll go ahead and take Nei up on
her offer and freshen up a bit.
I had a feeling you'd be awake.
My body is starting to move on its own.
I forgot.
Miss Kyoka hasn't given me my reward yet.
How are you? I'm fine.
I'm feeling pretty great myself.
They say you're the one who saved me.
Thanks a lot, Yuki.
We all work together.
That's very true.
This victory was earned
by all the defense force.
Especially you.
Fighting back even after being consumed?
You were stubborn as ever.
The thought of letting her absorb
all of my power got me so pissed!
Perfect timing since we're all here.
You can lend me a hand
with the debriefing.
I'm sorry, Mira.
The debriefing will have to wait.
What the hell?!
What's more important?!
His reward is starting.
Give us a minute.
I intend to reward him as well.
What the hell for?
It's like you said, this victory
belongs to the Demon Defense Force.
So really?
Those who are able to reward him should!
Is that truly the issue here?
He did go out of his way
to rescue me himself, so...
I'll...
I'll help with the reward.
Quit pressuring yourself.
From the looks of it, it seems
like we'll be taking a bath.
A bath?
We don't even share a charnel!
There's no way!
What the hell, Tenka?
Your body isn't moving on its own!
How are you not losing
your mind about this?
I can't get undressed!
It's too embarrassing!
And I was the one who suggested it!
I can't believe this is happening!
I'm so nervous I'm
paralyzed are you starting
to feel dizzy i think
you may be a little shy
Doing stuff like this in
a hot spring you pervert
You did so great out there
There's something that
you should really know!
What is it?
A god living on inside of Yuki.
It sounds harmless enough.
It's difficult to tell
whether it was just a dream.
Right.
I can't even talk to her right now anyway.
I promise to always watch out for you.
We'll see how it all plays out.
Report anything unusual.
Yes, ma 'am.
No!
I still can't do it!
in anticipation of the
eight thunder gods next
attack kyoka and mira
held a post-mortem after
the battle with kusetsu
they focused on mira's
loss carefully reflecting
on what factors caused
yep in the end i shouldn't have come
at her head on only because you had to
save all of those innocent people as
a commander i wish i could have taken
down a god everything turned out fine
in the end though and i refuse to
settle for less as talented as miss
mira is she's extremely hard on herself.
Hey, Kyoka.
I want to borrow Yuki.
Yes, yes,
yes
Let's
go!
This little story is
about a dream Yuki had.
High school?
What am I doing here?
What's up?
Quit zoning out first
thing in the morning.
Uh, sorry about that!
Huh?
Hey there, underclassmen!
Hey!
Lessons are starting!
Get to class!
Why the heck is everyone a student?
This is your mind, so I'm able
to make things like this happen.
Stop messing with my head!
As I'm combing through your memories,
I see you didn't have a girlfriend
while you were in school.
I'll be your girlfriend, Yuki.
We can pick up where we left off.
What?
What's going on?
My body's moving on its own again.
Play it cool.
There's a ton of questions
I still need to ask.
I have to try and stop this
before it goes too far!
He escaped!
Yuki Cuts Class
Next time, Episode 12, Gods Assemble!
Here's today's bonus!
We welcome you all to the
Slave High School! Oh no!
You don't have a girlfriend?
Well, in that case, I'll be a girlfriend.
It'll be thrilling.